A Guide to the William H. Kiblinger Papers, 1855-2000
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
William H. Kiblinger Papers, 1855-2000
Library of Virginia
39455
26.5 cubic feet and 3 volumes
William H. Kiblinger
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Janice L. Abercrombie, Mineral, Virginia, 4 April 2002.
Biographical/Historical Information
William Henry Kiblinger was born on 29 January 1918 in Mineral, Louisa County, Virginia. He was the son of George Edgar Kiblinger (1877-1948) and Maggie May Lavinia Butler (1879-1951). During World War II, Kiblinger served as a Master Sergeant in the 246 Coast Artillery Corps at Fort Monroe and Fort Story, Virginia, and later with the 3169 Signal Service Group in New Guinea, the Philipines, and Okinawa. After the war, he worked in communications for the federal government. He never married. During his retirement, he worked on family genealogy, researched local history, pursued photography, and was an amateur radio operator. Kiblinger died on 23 January 2001.
Scope and Content Information
Papers, 1855-2000 (bulk 1940-2000), of William Henry Kiblinger (1918-2001) of Mineral, Louisa County, Virginia. The bulk of the collection dates from 1940-2000. Includes historical files on the town of Mineral and Louisa County, Virginia, family research files, notebooks, correspondence and subject files, photographs, oversize material, and other items.
Organization
Organized into the following six series: I. Mineral/Louisa County History Files; II. Family Research Files; III. Notebooks; IV. Correspondence and Subject Files; V. Photographs; VI. Oversize and Other Items.
Contents List
- Mineral/Louisa County History Files (Box 1-10)
  This series contains information accumulated by Kiblinger during his research on local history. The files include drafts of articles he wrote and published, and research on prominent individuals, places, and events. There is material on mines and the mining industry, schools, including a run of graduation announcements and programs, churches, and local businesses. There is also a substantial amount of information on the Davis, Harper, Hendrick, Sims, Walton, and Whitlock families. This series contains abstracts of census, deed, and marriage records, tombstone inscriptions, maps, published sources, and other materials.
  - Adams (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aerial Maps (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Aerial Maps - Mineral and Contrary Creek (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Aerial Maps - Order Forms (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aerial View of Louisa (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alhizer (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allah Cooper Mine (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arminius Mines (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arminius Mines - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Article - Chiswell (in progress) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Article - The Crenshaw Sulphur Mine (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Article - Cuzco (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Article - The Rough and Ready Iron Furnace (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Article - The Rough and Ready Turnout (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Article - Tolersville P.O. Tavern/Reuben B. Davis (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Article - Tramroad: Victoria Furnace to Tolersville (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Article - The Victoria Furnace (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Belvin (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Berryman (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bickers, James Franklin, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bishop-Bickers (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bishop. Walter (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Burgess Postcard Collection (Mineral Area Scenes) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Business of Mining and its Influence on Mineral, Virginia by James R. McCloud, Jr. (July 1996) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - C & O Railway Tracks - Mineral (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Cemeteries (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Census - 1850 - Louisa County (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Chaplin (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Chiswell Mine Patent (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Church of the Incarnation (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cole (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Coleman, Chaplin & Burch (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Contrary Creek (North Branch) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Contrary Creek Lands (Deeds and Plats) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Contrary" Plantation (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - County Maps - Mineral Area (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Courthouse Move From Louisa to Mineral, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cuzco Landmarks (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Davis (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Davis, Abraham (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Davis-Harris-Thomasson-Barnett (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Davis, Reuben B. & Abraham (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Reuben B. Davis Cemetery (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Deeds - Abraham H. Davis to Reuben B. Davis (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Davis Turnout/Tram Road (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dunn (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Early County Schools (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
  - Ennis, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Estes (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Fleming (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Foster (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Gold (Va. Reduction Works and Mining Company) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Gooch-Toler Connection (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Grace Adams Davis Park Dedication, 22 May 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Graduation Announcements and Programs, 1910-1919 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Graduation Announcements and Programs, 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Graduation Announcements and Programs, 1930-1939 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Graduation Announcements and Programs, 1940-1949 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Graduation Announcements and Programs, 1979, 1982, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Grady (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Grasberger (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Grooms-Bowles (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Gunter (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hambleton/Hamilton (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Harlow - Census (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Harper (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - Harper - Census (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Harris (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Nathan Harris Cemetery (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Harris - Census (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Harris Chapel (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Harris Tract (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Haynes (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Heads of Household - Louisa County [1785?] (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hendrick (Box 4, Folder 9-13)
  - Hendrick Deeds (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hendrick Homes in Kentucky (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hendrick, James (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hendrick, William (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Hendrick, William W. (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
  - The Hendricks and Their Kin by Jasper R. Hendrick (1962) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hester (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hiter (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Johnson (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Lewis H. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Jordan (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Julia Mine - Woodlawn Cemetery (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Keller (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kendrick (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kennon (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Lacy (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Letterheads (Copies) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Letterheads (Originals) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Louisa County and the War Between the States (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Louisa County Bicentennial Festival Day - 22 May 1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Louisa County Corporations - Mining and Other (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Louisa County Deed Abstracts (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Louisa County Directory, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Louisa County History (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Louisa County/Mineral Historic Mine and Furnace Study, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Louisa County - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Louisa County Postmasters (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Louisa County, Virginia: Archaeological Resources Related to Mining and Early Industry (2000) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Louisa County, Virginia: Archaeological Resources Related to Mining and Early Industry (2000) - DRAFT (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Louisa County Women's Club (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Louisa Railroad (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Maps and Plats (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - Maps - Civil War Era (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Maps - Contrary Creek and Tolersville Area (1963) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Maps - Louisa County (Roads) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Maps of Mines Near Mineral City (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Maucher - Census (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Mine Accidents (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mine Deeds and Plats (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Mine Stock Certificates (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Mineral Baptist Church (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Mineral - Baseball Teams (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Mineral City - Business Lots (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Mineral City - Businesses (Billheads) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mineral City - Churches (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
  - Mineral City - Deeds (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Mineral City - Maps, ca. 1890 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mineral City Mining, Manufacturing and Land Company (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Mineral City - Notes (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mineral - Deaths, 1920-1950 (Safley Funeral Home) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mineral - People (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Mineral High School - Classes of 1934 and 1935 Reunions (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Mineral High School - Diplomas and Certificates (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Mineral High School - First Graduating Class (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mineral High School - Graduates, 1911-1940 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Mineral High School - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Mineral High School - The Prospector (1938) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Mineral Hotel (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Mineral Prospectus (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Mineral - Street Renaming (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Mineral Telephone Directory, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Mineral/Tolersville Centennial/Bicentennial Celebration, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
  - Miners' Descendants - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Mines - Census Records (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Mines and Mining - General Information (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Mines - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Nelson (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Nelson, William C. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Noel (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Official Company Seals, Tracings, etc. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Parish Register (copy) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Parrish (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Pedigree Chart of Dolly Lorraine Garrett (b. 1912) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Pendleton (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Plats - Contrary Creek Area (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Porter (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Post Offices and Postmarks (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Pottiesville Store Ledger, 1818 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Pyrite-Gold Belt in Louisa and Spotsylvania Counties (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Quarles (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Rough and Ready Furnace and its Railroad (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Safley Funeral Home Register, 1920-1951 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Scarrots Meeting House (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Schmitz (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Schools (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Shealor/Sheelor (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Simms/Sims (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sims - Census (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Sims Property (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Slate Hill Gold Mine (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Smith - Census (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Boyd M. Smith Mine (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Spicer (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Spicer - Census (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Story of Old Tolersville - Material and Notes (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Stout (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sulphur Mines (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Talley (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Tanyard Branch Aerial Photograph (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - The Tavern Cottage (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Thomas, Sarah - Will, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Toler Family (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Toler, William F. - Deeds and Tavern Licenses (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Tolersville Depot Plans (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Tolersville Notes (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Tolersville - Plats (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Tolersville Post Office (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Towsey, Richard R. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Tribble - Census (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Trice (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Trinity Baptist Church (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Trinity Meeting House (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Tulloh (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Victoria Furnace Sulphur Mine Area (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Victoria Iron Furnace (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
  - Virginia Reduction Works and Mining Company (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Waldrop (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Walton (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Walton Gold Mine (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Walton, William (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Ware (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Whitlock (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Whitlock, Jesse C. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Winston, Frank V. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Woodlawn Cemetery (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
  - Woodlawn Plantation (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Family Research Files (Box 11-16)
  This series includes information gathered by Kiblinger on the genealogy of the Butler, Kiblinger, and allied families. Of particular note in this series are papers relating to the Civil War service of William Carpenter Kiblinger (1831-1908) who served in the 10th Virginia Infantry. Included are letters written to his wife describing camp life and battles, a furlough pass, amnesty oath, currency, and other items. This series also contains abstracts of census records, deeds, orders, and wills, as well as correspondence, tombstone inscriptions, and plats and surveys. There are copies of a family newsletter he published for a short time, and also a genealogy he compiled with Earl R. Savage in 1998. This series documents lines of his family which settled in Rockingham County and Louisa Counties, Virginia, and Indiana, Ohio, and Texas.
  - Butler (Box 11, Folder 1-9)
  - Butler - Census Abstracts (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Descendants of John G. Butler and Mary Thacker (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Butler Family Group Sheets (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Butler, Maggie May Lavinia (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Butler, Maggie May Lavinia - Papers (Class Writing Exercises) (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
  - Descendants of Samuel Butler (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Descendants of Samuel and Elizabeth Butler of Louisa County (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Butler Society (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Cemeteries - Butler/Kiblinger (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Census Notes - Allied Families (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Cross Keys Farms (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Kiblinger (Box 12, Folder 11-14)
  - Kiblinger (Box 13, Folder 1-8)
  - Kiblinger Car (Auburn, Indiana) (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
  - Kiblinger - Census (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Kiblinger - Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Kiblinger - Cross Keys (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Kiblinger - Deeds (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Kiblinger Family Bible Records (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Kiblinger Family Group Sheets (Box 14, Folder 3-5)
  - Kiblinger Farm Plats and Surveys (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Kiblinger Genealogy - Cypert, Yvonne (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Kiblinger - Germany (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
  - Kiblinger - Indiana and Ohio (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Kiblinger Inquiries and Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Kiblinger, Jacob (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Kiblinger, Jacob - Tavern (Trevilian's Depot) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Kiblinger, Johan Daniel (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Kiblinger-Kyger (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Kiblinger - Maps and Plats (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Kiblinger - Marriage Bonds (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Kiblinger - Marriages (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kiblinger Material (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Kiblinger - Melton Tract/Trevilian's Depot (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Kiblinger - Personal Contacts - Notes from Their Memory (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Kiblinger - Rockingham Historical Society (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Kiblinger - Rockingham County Map, 1885 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Kiblinger - Texas Branch (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Kiblinger - Trevilian's Depot Deed (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Kiblinger, William C. - Civil War Service (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Descendants of William Carpenter Kiblinger (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Kib's Kousins Newsletter - Proofs, Mailing List, etc. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Kib's Kousins Newsletter (Vol. 1, no. 1 - Vol. 3, no. 4) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Kublinger (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Kublinger - Copies (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Kublinger, Jacob - Will, 1817 (copy) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Kublinger Tree - Johan Jacob & Johan Daniel (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Descendants of Johann Jacob Kublinger (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The American Descendants of Peter Kublinger by Earl Roland Savage and William Henry Kiblinger (1998) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Descendants of Peter Kublinger (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Revolutionary War Claims (Butler/Kiblinger) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Savage, Earl R. (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Notebooks (Box 17-20a)
  This series contains notes which Kiblinger accumulated during his research on local history and genealogy. They are arranged alphabetically by topic, although many of the notebooks contain numerous subjects. Among the more prominent topics are the Butler, Hendrick, Keller, and Kiblinger families, and notes on Contrary Creek and various local mines. Data contained in the notebooks included abstracts of census records, marriage records, information from deed and will books, and tombstone inscriptions.
  - Butler (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - Butler Data, Louisa County Deaths, and Walton Data (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Butler/Essex County (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Butler/Kiblinger (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Butler/King William County (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Butler Marriages (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Butler Wills, Deeds, Marriages (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Census - Elkhart County, IN and Rockingham County, VA (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Chancery Final Decrees (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Chiswell/Contrary Plantation (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Contrary Creek Lands/Hendrick Deeds (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Contrary Plantation, Deeds, etc. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Cooper's Mill Deeds (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Deed and Will Book Abstracts (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Deeds (Kiblinger/Porter) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Hambleton/Hendrick (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Hendrick/Butler (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Hendrick/Johnson (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Keller Rockingham/Augusta Census & Marriages and Davis Family Data (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Kiblinger (Ohio/Indiana) (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Kiblinger Research (Box 18, Folder 8-11)
  - Louisa County Marriages (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Louisa County Occupations/Butler Family Census Records (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Louisa Railroad (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Mineral City Lots/Allah Cooper Mine (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Mines on Contrary Creek (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Order and Minute Books, Marriages, Wills, Deeds (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Reuben B. Davis Cemetery (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Surveys/Kiblinger Farm & Adjoining Lands (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Various Subjects (Box 19, Folder 6-12)
  - 1860 Federal Census - Louisa County (Selected) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 1870 Federal Census - Louisa County (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 1870/1880 Federal Census - Louisa County (Occupations) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 1880 Federal Census - Louisa County (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 1880 Federal Census - Louisa County (Incomplete) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - 1900 Federal Census - Louisa County (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
  - 1900/1910 Federal Census - Louisa County (Selected) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 1910 Federal Census - Louisa County (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
  - 1910 Federal Census - Louisa County (Box 20a, Folder 1)
  - 1920 Federal Census - Louisa County (Box 20a, Folder 2-3)
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1858-1999 (Box 21-29)
  These are basically Kiblinger's personal files. The correspondence is family related. There are many letters written by him to his sister and parents while he was in the service during World War II. Also included in this series are accounts and receipts, information on amateur radio, his Army service, the Civilian Conservation Corps, clippings, funeral programs, invitations, report cards, and other miscellaneous family-related materials.
  - Correspondence, 1858-1859 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1862-1868 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1870-1879 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1881, 1885-1888 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1890-1894 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1895-1899 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1900-1905 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1906-1907 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1908-1909 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1910-1913 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1914-1919 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1920-1924 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1925-1929 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1930-1939 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1943 (January-May) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1943 (June-December) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1944 (February) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1944 (March) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1944 (April-December) (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1945 (June-July) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1945 (August-December) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1959, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Account Book, 1898 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Accounts and Receipts (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
  - Agreements (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Almanacs (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Amateur Radio (Box 23, Folder 6-8)
  - Army Records - MSgt William H. Kiblinger (Box 23, Folder 9-10)
  - Autograph Book - Sarah E. Kiblinger, 1933-1934 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Bank Book, 1959-1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Birthday Cards (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - C & O Historical Society (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - C & O Railway - Depot Plans, Agents, etc. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Calling Cards (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Cancelled Checks (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Census Order Forms (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Certificates (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Chancery Final Decrees (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Ciphering Book (copy) (Box 24, Folder 11-12)
  - Civilian Conservation Corps (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Clark County (OH) Historical Society (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Class Attendance Lists (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Clippings (Box 25, Folder 5-12)
  - Court Records (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Deeds (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - DialAmerica Marketing, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Enlisted Record and Record of Separation (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Envelopes (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Estate of Robert B. Cook (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Currency (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Funeral Programs (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - German Script (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Greeting Cards (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Gulf War (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Hanover County Court Record Abstracts (1979) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Harrisonburg-Rockingham County Historical Society - Newsletters and Other Publications (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
  - Invitations (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Invoices - Arminius Chemical Co. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Iron Furnaces in Virginia (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Kiblinger, William H. - Personal (Box 27, Folder 10-12)
  - Library Inventory List, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Metro Rail System - Washington, DC (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 15-16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous Research Notes (Box 28, Folder 3-5)
  - Morse Telegraph Club (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Names, Addresses, Birthdays (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - New House, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters - Genealogical and Historical Societies (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Patents (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Physical Fitness Certificates (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Poetry (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Promissory Notes (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - RF & P Railroad (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Railroad Schedules (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Railroads - Plats and Depot Tracks (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Receipts - Coleman & Chaplin, 1914-1915 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Register of Names of Men Buried in Confederate Cemetery, Spotsylvania C.H., Va., War 1861-1864 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Report Cards (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
  - Research Projects (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Resolutions of Respect, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Route 522 Project (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Sale of Kiblinger Land, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Tax Receipts (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Taxes (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - University College of Medicine Commencement, 1911 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Valentines (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - VEPCO Power Line - Kiblinger Farm (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Wedding Invitations (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Photographs (Box 30-53)